Wealth. Fame. Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all?
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
So you're a pirate?
Uh-huh.
Is that why you went and did a crazy thing
like shoot a cannonball
into the restaurant?
That was an accident.
It was self-defense that
turned into a stray shot.
A stray shot?
In any case, you really don't want
to do anything stupid to this place.
The owner used to be a cook
in a famous pirate fleet.
Oh, so the old man used to be a pirate.
The restaurant is everything
to that crazy old man.
It's the only treasure he'll
need for the rest of his life.
He'll do anything to protect it,
on top of which all of the
cooks who joined him out of
respect and admiration are just
as hot-headed as any pirate.
Which helps, since pirates are always
coming and going out of this place.
Yeah, notice that.
This is a really wild restaurant, huh?
So true.
And this is how it is every day.
It's gotten so bad that
customers are coming here
just to watch fights between
the cooks and the pirates.
Every day it's been a new
pirate ship and a new rampage.
It wasn't long till all the
waiters got scared and bailed.
Ah, that makes sense.
So that's why the old man wanted
me to work for him for a year.
So, you joining my pirate crew or what?
I'm sorry, but I can't.
There's a reason I have to
work here in the restaurant,
and so I can't just walk away from it.
No way! I don't accept!
You don't accept?
It's very simple.
I refuse to accept your refusal.
You're a good cook, and I need one,
so it's obvious that we
should be pirates together.
Listen to what I'm saying.
I can't leave here, all right?
What's your reason for saying I
don't have to tell you anything?
What the but you just
said to listen to you!
I told you my answer was no and that's
all you need to hear from me now!
Take your pirate ship and find a cook
someplace else before I cut you up, Straw Hat!
You listen to me, jerk!
No one makes fun of my Straw Hat
unless they're ready for a beating.
I'm sorry to interrupt
What is it?
My name is Ginny and I'm a
crew member of Don Krieg's
pirate fleet and you say
that you're a pirate yourself
What is it you seek?
Oh, the one piece.
And pretty soon, I'm going to
sail the Grand Line and find it.
Well, you can't have
been seeking it for long.
If you don't even have a cook yet,
your crew can't be all that big.
Nope, he's only the fifth member.
I told you I'm not
going, so don't count me!
You seem like a nice kid, so let me
give you some friendly advice, okay?
The Grand Line is a
place you want to avoid.
You're still young, there's
no need to rush into anything.
Remember, the Grand Line is one
small part of this entire ocean.
If you want to be a real pirate,
there are plenty of other places
out here on the seas to explore.
Hmm, I see.
Well, why don't you just tell me
what to avoid in the Grand Line now?
I can't.
I don't know anything.
I don't understand it.
And that is why I fear it.
For being a crew member of Don Krieg's,
you're a pretty wimpy pirate. Hmm?
Who's Don Krieg?
The appetizer for table three is ready.
Yeah.
Well, you're gonna have
to take it out yourself.
The last waiter's gone.
You think more of them will be coming?
Patty. Who knows?
I heard the guy you beat up earlier in
the restaurant was one of Don Krieg's men.
I don't think that will make
the rest of them very happy.
I don't care whose man he was.
All I'm saying is the stories I've heard.
say Don Krieg is the strongest,
fiercest, and most evil pirate
in this part of the ocean.
He is.
On these waters, his grip of
fear reaches far and wide.
He commands over 50 pirate captains, one
of the largest pirate fleets ever seen.
He is truly a monster.
He doesn't scare me.
I've heard that his extraordinary fleet
of ships has more than 5,000 pirates.
this could be bad for boss if if
that guy you beat up goes to don
krieg and tells him what you did
and he sends just one ship there
won't be enough of us to fight
them off we'll be crushed like a
grape under an elephant and left
to sink to the bottom of the ocean
you're saying i should
have just served them so
we could experience our
great customer service
and meals for free you
don't think that would have
been rude to the other
damn crooks who pay money
I would never stoop that
low This is the Baratier The
fighting cooks have a
reputation to uphold Don't we?
I'd never ruin that.
I don't care who that pirate cries to!
Let them send their ships.
I'll fight them all off!
If you're scared, quit and
let the real cooks work.
Don't you dare say that to me!
I'm tired of all the
big talk you spit out.
Which is why all the waiters jumped ship.
Everything that's happening now
is all your fault, Patty? Please!
Those waiters were worthless wimps
the moment a customer showed up.
Worthless whips!
Go for it!
Take him out, Carney!
It doesn't stand a chance, Patty!
All right, what's all this?
Get back to work already!
Yes, boss, Sam!
So long, then.
Thanks for the warning, but I'm
still gonna go to the Grand Line.
I know.
Do whatever you want.
I'm just a stranger, and I can't stop you!
from going anywhere you want to go.
I just wanted to give you a fair warning.
And to you, chef?
Thank you for everything you saved
my life and I owe you for that.
Your cooking skills are
the best I've ever seen.
I hope to come back again sometime.
I'll have a seat for you.
Sure, boy.
Get up here right now!
Boss, you're hard to find.
Hey, Gain? Go.
Sorry.
You'll probably get yelled at or fired?
because you gave me that food for free.
Whatever.
Now there's not proof, sir.
There's no way for me to get yelled at.
Try not to get caught again, you hear?
Thank you again, Chef Sanji.
I will never forget your kindness.
Sanji! Chorboy!
Get back to work already!
Hey!
Table 3 is ready!
Hey, guys!
My name's Luffy and I'm gonna
be the new Chorboy around here!
Nice to meet all of you!
What happened to that dessert?
Which one of us was supposed to make that?
It was supposed to be him.
I don't have time to make that.
I'm too busy.
You're too busy being injured.
Say that again. I dare you.
Don't you sit there picking your nose?
Go wash the dishes or something.
Right now.
Has anyone seen Sanji?
I think I saw him hitting on a customer.
Again?
I wish Boss Zef would get rid of him.
It's bad enough he's the Zeus chef, but
he's never in the kitchen doing his job.
I think we're stuck with him.
He's worked here longer than any of us.
He was working the kitchen and the
dining room even before I started.
Yeah, but even so, I just don't get it.
Why does he stay here when he
and Boss Zephyr always fighting?
I think he wants to be the head chef.
Huh?
Huh? Hmm?
Chore boy!
Just how many of these dishes have
you gone and broken into tiny pieces?
You know what?
I forgot to count! Aw, man!
I wasn't being serious, you idiot!
Why are you breaking them?
Stop screwing around
and clean up your mess!
That I can do!
Stop!
Don't take the food!
What's wrong with you?
That was a perfect entree!
Yep, pretty tasty!
Why don't we have you take
orders in the dining room?
Just ask the customers
what they want to eat.
Is that simple enough?
Yes.
These chores sure are boring.
I wonder if Kobe got tired
of all this work, too.
Chore boy!
Ugh!
What are you doing?
We heard you had to work
here for a whole year.
Is that okay if we redraw
the flag for our ship?
You're eating all this
delicious food without me?
What kind of crew are you?
Who could you do this to me?
Hold on.
I think that's our
business, isn't that right?
Take this. Oh, boy.
This is going to be so good.
You know, I have to say the food
here really is quite delicious.
Good stuff.
Yes, it is.
I feel bad for you, but...
You should be drinking this yourself!
I can't believe you did that!
Yeah, well, I can't believe you did that!
Oh, that was nasty!
Aren't they quaint?
I wonder if that's the rest of his crew.
Finish pouring it yourself.
Oh, dear Ocean, thank you for this treasure
you have shared from your depths. Huh?
Ah, yes, my love.
I can't bear this hardship
of loving you from afar.
It is too difficult.
I am now prepared to sail to the
ends of the earth as a pirate!
If it means someone of your rare beauty?
will be by my side.
To be together sailing the seas.
But how tragic a great
obstacle blocks our way.
That great obstacle would be me, right?
Sanji.
Ah, stupid geezer.
This is an opportunity
you don't want to pass up.
Why not join them and become a pirate?
I have no need to keep
you here at my restaurant.
I see.
This cook saved your life, and you
were able to return here to us.
Is that what you're saying, Ginny?
Yes, but you see, I had no idea the main
ship was in this condition, Don Krieg.
No idea.
So what now?
Now I believe I'll take you to
the sea restaurant, Baratier.
Hey, listen, pal.
I'm the Zeus chef in this place.
What do you mean you
don't need me anymore?
You fight with customers all the time.
You flirt with every woman
under 80 who walks through here.
You can't even cook a decent meal.
You're worth less to me
than the chum after brunch.
That's what I mean.
So, uh...
Oh, and let's not forget about how the other
cooks avoid you like you were poisoned.
So just run off and be a pirate or
whatever, but get out of this restaurant.
That's how it is?
You shoot off at the mouth and expect
that I'm just going to take it, old man?
I could blow off everything you said,
but I won't listen to anyone trash my
cooking I'm staying here as a Zeus chef,
and that's final.
You hear me?
What do you think you're doing
grabbing your boss by the collar?
You can
try
to kick me out
But I'm here to stay.
I'm not going anywhere, old man.
Not till you're dead and gone.
Dead?
I got another hundred years of
kicking your ass left in me.
He's always got to have
the last word. See?
He said it's cool.
Now you can become a pirate.
Shut up!
My apologies.
I hope I can make it up to you with this
delightful fruit Macedonia, my princess.
Wow, you're too kind.
It looks wonderful. Good.
Hey, don't forget about us, Mr.
Casanova.
We'd better get some
kind of an apology, too!
This tea should be more
than adequate for you.
In fact, you should be thanking me.
What?
You want to fight?
You're going to regret this!
Take him out, Zoro!
You take him out.
Stop it!
Please don't fight because of me!
Of course, my dear.
Who said it was about you?
I wanted to tell you that all of
the food here is just delicious.
But it's a little too expensive for me.
Relax, it's free!
Oh, thank you!
You guys still got to pay, though.
How very generous of you.
What are you sitting around for?
You're not here to lounge around. Right.
It's them.
They're here.
The hourglasses mean our time is up.
What are we gonna do?
Now that flag means death.
There's no doubt.
It belongs to the ruler of the east.
Blue Don Krieg!
But why?
Why have the creek pirates come here?
I told you.
I knew those goons would show up.
Now.
Are you gonna get rid
of those guys or what?
This can't be real.
He's got a whole fleet to command.
Why would Tang Creek come here
to get revenge for just one man?
I mean, doesn't he have
anything better to do?
He's here, all right.
We're not imagining that ship, are we?
Guys, don't panic, but I think
this is our cue to leave right now.
Look at the sheer size of that galleon.
What a huge ship.
You think Ginny came back to
repay you for your kindness?
I seriously doubt that's it.
It's something else.
Hey, look!
Yeah, there's Shamp.
Whoa, what'd they do?
Sail through a hurricane or something?
It doesn't seem like damage
inflicted by cannons.
In fact, it doesn't look man-made at all.
Then maybe it was a tornado hurricane.
There he is.
I beg you I need food and water.
We have money.
Lots of money.
No, this can't be.
Where's the death and destruction?
Is this really the Don Krieg,
Commodore of the Grand Pirate Fleet?
Guess he's hungry.
Uh, uh, uh, uh,
C-Captain!
Uh, Don Krieg!
Please help him!
Our captain is on the brink of starvation!
He could die!
He hasn't had a single
bite to eat for days.
He'll die if he doesn't
get some food soon.
This is great!
I haven't laughed that
hard in a long time!
The great Don Creek kneeling before us.
We have some money.
We're here as customers this time.
Do you really think I'm that stupid?
Hey, get a hold of the Marines right away.
What?
He's finally weak enough to be captured.
This may never happen again,
and I'm not going to ruin it by
helping him get his strength back.
He's right.
Who knows what he'll do if
he gets on his feet again.
He's done terrible things.
And as soon as he's up,
he'll keep on doing them.
I say we let him starve.
Once he's back to normal, he'll kill
every last person in this restaurant.
He won't get so much as
a glass of water from me.
I won't do anything.
Once I eat, I promise I'll leave quietly.
So please, be merciful and help me.
You're a king, Dunkrieg. Stop it.
Please don't reduce yourself to this.
You're better than a
common beggar, please sir.
What about your pride?
I've promised
Please I'll take the scraps.
I'll take anything
Anything
Don
Yeah, boo-hoo for the cruel
pirate hey step aside Paddy?
Sanji!
Here's something for your captain.
Thank you, Sanji.
Thank you.
You dimwit get that food
away from him right now!
Don't you realize he's a cold
heartless killing machine?
This is the man known as the ruler of the
east blue the most
treacherous of all pirates!
It all started back in prison he pretended
to be a marine and when
he decided to declare
his pirate ambitions he took command of a
marine vessel by killing
the senior officer!
He would raise the marine
flag to enter ports!
Then lay waste to the unsuspecting
cities and passenger ships there!
He even showed the white flag
before attacking enemy ships!
He did anything to secure victory!
That guy fights dirty!
He's also unmatched in physical combat!
You think he'll just leave us alone?
Look, I've got news for you.
That's not possible with a
bloodthirsty killer like him!
He deserves death!
Thanks!
Sanji!
This is not what we agreed on.
You gave me your word.
I only brought you here because you
promised that you wouldn't ruin this place.
Or hurt the man who saved us.
Yes, that was delicious.
I feel alive again.
Hey, you see that?
It looks bad.
What do you think is going on in there?
Don't know.
Let's go inside and see.
What?
Are you serious?
This is a pretty good ship.
I believe that I'll take it.
Right.
I see.
As you can all see, my ship is a wreck.
Naturally, I'll be needing a nice new one.
After a few small chores, every last one
of you will leave the ship. What? No!
Don Krieg, you promised! Please!
There are about a hundred
men left on board my ship.
All are weak with hunger.
And many are seriously wounded.
If you value your lives, you will prepare
food and water for every last one of them.
I've lost too many men to hunger already.
Water!
Bring them over! Immediately!
You're telling us to
feed our executioners?
Do you hear how stupid that sounds?
We refuse!
You refuse?
Jews, I wasn't asking you.
Now make no mistake, you wretched cook.
I'm not placing an order.
I am giving you one.
Do I make myself clear?
Don't defy me!
Sanji.
Sanji. Sorry.
I didn't mean for this to happen. You see?
Look what you brought on this
restaurant you stupid bastard
Hey, where do you think you're going?
To the kitchen
Looks like I'll be cooking
a hundred more meals today.
Sanji! Sanji!
What?
Are you crazy?
Good.
Hop to it.
Tell me the truth, Sanji!
Are you his spy or something?
We can't let you go
anywhere near that kitchen.
We're fed up with you acting insane.
All right.
Stop me if you wish.
I know.
It's no secret that Don Krieg
is a terrible, ruthless man.
But that doesn't matter to me.
It doesn't matter.
After we feed all these men, who
knows what's going to happen?
I am just a simple cook,
no more and no less.
If someone's going hungry,
it's my duty to feed them.
That's all I know.
What do you say?
Is that wrong?
Penny!
Hey, somebody grab him!
You bring free food to the bums I kick
out of this place over and over again.
And I'm not about to argue over who's
right in that particular situation,
but this time you're just
flat out wrong, Sanji.
I can't let you do
things like that anymore.
We're going to protect this place.
Fortunately, we've got
numbers on our side.
It is Don Krieg, but what
could he do against all of us?
At a joint like this, pirate
scumbags come and go all day.
We're fully prepared to
serve any kind of customer.
Is that...
I really hope you saved
some room for dessert.
Cause I have a secret recipe. Huh?
That is truly to die for!
Open wide!
Here comes the meatball of doom!
Don!
I might have broken the door.
I sure hope Zef doesn't yell at me again.
They might go easy on you for
saving the restaurant and all.
So what are we going to do about
all the guys left in Krieg's ship?
Fry them!
Cover it and batter and
fry the entire thing!
Are you a chef or a comedian?
because your jokes are lame.
And that dessert was terrible.
The worst I ever had.
So die!
He's got them everywhere.
All those guns.
You cooks should not have defied me!
I am by far the world's strongest man!
Arms made of solid steel,
wood-steel body armor, impenetrable?
and a diamond fist that can
pound this entire world to dust!
in addition to the weapons
on my body I have a
fleet of 50 ships with
5,000 pirates my record is
perfect I've won every
single battle that I've
ever been in I am Don and
I'm the only one fit to be
called Don out of the way
when I give you slime balls
in order you will follow
it down to the last ladder
don't ever disobey me this
is about a hundred meals
now take it to your men
right away no owner Zeff
you're redfoot Zeff
what are you doing you can't
be serious if all of those
pirates get their strength
back the restaurant will be
completely taken over that
would be true if they still
had the will to fight tell me
did your will survive defeat
that can't be the great Don Creek was
defeated oh not even he could do it a
pirate fleet with 50
ships couldn't make it
on the Grand Line the Grand
Line it It is you, isn't it?
You're Redfoot Zeff.
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure!
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me!
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go!
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever changes?
I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream.